http://www.bbcamerica.com/privacy

xBBC AmericaBy BBC AmericaGET IT NOW
This browser is supported only in Windows 10 and above.
Privacy
AMC NETWORKS PRIVACY POLICY
EFFECTIVE DATE: November 4th, 2020
1. WHAT IS THE SCOPE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY?
2. WILL THIS POLICY EVER CHANGE?
3. WHAT INFORMATION IS COLLECTED?
4. HOW IS MY INFORMATION USED?
5. WHEN IS MY INFORMATION DISCLOSED?
6. WHAT ARE MY CHOICES?
7. HOW LONG DO YOU KEEP MY INFORMATION?
8. WHAT ABOUT LINKS TO THIRD PARTY WEBSITES?
9. HOW IS MY INFORMATION PROTECTED?
10. WHAT IF MY INFORMATION IS INCORRECT?
11. WHAT IS YOUR POLICY REGARDING CHILDREN?
12. CALIFORNIA RIGHTS.
13. GOVERNING LAW.
14. WHERE IS MY INFORMATION STORED AND PROCESSED?
15. HOW CAN I CONTACT YOU?
1. WHAT IS THE SCOPE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY?
This Privacy Policy describes what information AMC Networks Inc. and its United States-based affiliate and subsidiary companies (together, “AMC” or “we” and sometimes “us”) collect about you and why, how we use and share that information, and the choices we offer.
This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) is incorporated into the AMC Terms of Service, and applies to information that we collect when you sign up for, use, access, download or otherwise interact with any AMC applications, mobile applications, games, sweepstakes, products, services, or websites and anywhere else where this policy is posted, including applications we make available on third party sites or platforms, if disclosed to you in connection with your use of the application (collectively, “Services”), as well as when we collect information from other parties or from you at conferences or other offline interactions. If you disagree with the terms of this Policy, please do not use the Services.
Back To Top
2. WILL THIS POLICY EVER CHANGE?
We may change this Policy from time to time.  If we make changes, we will notify you by posting the updated policy and revising the “Effective Date” above.  Use of the Services after the posted Effective Date means you accept the current version of the Policy, including any changes made prior to the posted Effective Date. If we make any material changes to this Policy, we will also notify you by email or by means of a notice on the Services. We encourage you to review the Policy whenever you use our Services to stay informed about our information practices and the choices available to you.
Back To Top
3. WHAT INFORMATION IS COLLECTED?
We collect the following categories of information about you:
Identifiers, such as your name, e-mail address, phone number, and postal address;
Demographics, such as your gender and age;
Online activity information, such as your IP address or browsing history;
Location information that you provide or that we collect via your device, subject to your settings;
Inferences regarding preferences or other characteristics;
Transaction information, such as your cable provider, password, and viewing, subscription, and purchase histories or tendencies.
Payment information, such as payment card numbers; and
Audio, electronic, visual, olfactory, or similar information, such as photographs or voice recordings.
We collect personal information from you from a variety of sources, including:
From You: We collect information that you submit to us. When you personalize your profile, use the Services, or interact with us in other ways, including offline, we will collect any information you voluntarily provide, and we may also request optional information to support your use of the Services, such as a profile picture and birthday.  We collect any information that you voluntarily enter into any postings, comments or forums within the Services, including private messages you send to other users of the Services. If you send an e-mail to us, we will collect your e-mail address and the full content of your e-mail, including attached files and other information you choose to provide to us.  If you purchase a product or service through the Services, our third party payment processors will collect the billing and financial information they need to process your charges. This may include your postal address, email address and financial information. AMC does not directly collect or store your financial information, like credit card numbers. However, AMC’s third party payment processors may share non-financial information with us related to your purchases, like your name, shipping address and items purchased in order to fulfill your order.
From Your Devices:  When you use our Services, we may collect information about the devices you use to access the Services, including hardware model, operating system and version, Internet Protocol (“IP”) address and other unique device identifiers, mobile network information and information about the device’s interaction with our Services.  We also collect information about how you use our Services, including your access times, browser types and language.  This type of data enables us to understand how often individuals use parts of the Services so we can analyze and improve them.  To collect this information, we use cookies and web beacons, and other similar technologies.  To learn more about how we automatically receive and record information when you interact with the Services, please review our Cookies Policy.  This Privacy Policy covers only how we use information collected via cookies; it does not cover the use of such information by third parties.  However, options you have to control the use of third party cookies are explained in our Cookies Policy.
Location Information: We may collect different types of information about your location, including general information, such as the city, state and/or zip code associated with your IP Address, and, if you agree, more specific location information that is provided through the GPS functionality on mobile devices used to access the Services. We may use such location information to customize the Services, including advertising that is presented to you. For example, if you provide a zip code that indicates that you live in New York, the Services may be customized with New York-specific information, features, and advertisements. In order to do this, your location information may be passed along to our affiliates, agents, vendors or advertisers.  Options you have to control the automatic collection of location information are explained below under “What Are My Choices.”
Social Media Networks and Other Third Parties:  We may obtain information about you or your use of the Services from third parties and sources, such as our vendors, like web hosting providers, analytics providers or advertisers. You may give us permission to access your information from services offered by third parties, including social media networks.  For example, to access the Services, you may link your Facebook account to the Services, which allows us to obtain information from your Facebook account, such as your friends or contacts, profile picture, birthdate, gender, or other profile-related information and any other information you have opted to share with “everyone” on Facebook (or similar third party platform).  The information we obtain from third party services depends on your account/privacy settings with those third parties and the third parties’ privacy policies, so be sure to check those policies and to adjust your settings to meet your preferences. When you access the Services through social media networks and other third party platforms, you are authorizing AMC to collect, store and use such information and content in accordance with this Policy. Please keep in mind that any information provided to us by a third party may also be subject to that third party’s privacy policy.
Back To Top
4. HOW IS MY INFORMATION USED?
We use the information we collect to serve you and improve your experience with our Services. Some examples include:
to process your requests and provide you with services, information, or content;
to enable your access to the Services;
to provide, maintain, protect, develop and improve the Services, including through the use of statistical analysis;
to learn about how you use the Services, including by linking your activities across the devices you may use;
to customize the content and advertisements you receive from us and our trusted partners;
to communicate with you, including via email, text messages, social media, mail and phone;
to process your payments;
to learn about your interests and those of other consumers;
to protect our rights, your rights, and the rights others;
to administer your participation in contests or other promotions;
maintaining your account; and
to offer you additional information, opportunities, promotions and functionality from us or on our behalf, or from our partners or our advertisers.
We may aggregate or de-identify certain information that we collect from you. Aggregate and/or de-identified information is designed so that we cannot identify you personally.  We may use aggregated and/or de-identified data or other data that is not personally identifiable for any purpose, including without limitation in statistical analysis to help us analyze patterns in the use of the Services.
By accessing and using the Services, you consent to our use of your information about you in the manner described in this Policy.  If you do not agree or do not consent to the use of your information in these ways, you should not use the Services.
Back To Top
5. WHEN IS MY INFORMATION DISCLOSED?
We disclose information in the following circumstances
With your consent: We may share or disclose your information if you ask or authorize us to do so.
Among group companies:  We may share your information with our affiliated and subsidiary companies and joint venture partners for the purposes of processing, analyzing or storing your information or otherwise as needed to provide the Services to you or achieve other purposes for which we collect information, in each case, consistent with the terms of this Policy.
With service providers: We engage third party service providers to perform a variety of services and functions for us, such as data storage, transmitting emails, and managing digital content.  We may share your information with such service providers subject to confidentiality obligations consistent with this Policy and on the condition that the service providers use your information only on our behalf and pursuant to our instructions.
Information shared via third party social buttons, widgets and other embedded content: Some of our Services carry embedded content controlled by third parties for services such as social sharing, commenting and displaying video or images.  When you interact with these services they may collect information from and about you and your interaction with their content, including the URL of the web page you are visiting.  This activity will be subject to the privacy policy of and your settings for the third party network or service.  Please be aware that they may track your activity, including through the use of cookies or similar technology, without you needing to interact with them.  If this concerns you, ensure you log out of their services before using ours.
To comply with legal requirements and to protect you, us, and others: Notwithstanding anything to the contrary in this Policy, we reserve the right to retain and disclose your information at our discretion if we believe in good faith that such retention and disclosure is necessary to: (a) comply with relevant laws or to respond to subpoenas, warrants or similar process served on us; (b) protect and defend our rights or property, you, or third parties; or (c) ensure the safety and security of our Services, systems and of our customers and third parties.
In connection with a business transfer: In the event we go through a business transition such as a merger, acquisition by another company, bankruptcy, reorganization or sale of all or a portion of our assets, your information may be sold or transferred as part of that transaction. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur and are permitted by this Policy and that the new entity may continue to process your information as set forth in this Policy.
If the information has been aggregated, de-identified or otherwise does not identify you personally: We may share or disclose information that has been aggregated, de-identified, otherwise does not identify you or information that you choose to make public, such as your public user profile information.  For example, we may develop information concerning the Services’ users, using de-identification processes to help ensure that such information cannot reasonably be re-associated or connected with you as an individual.  This Policy does not limit our use or disclosure of de-identified information (i.e., information from which your name and any other personally identifying information has been removed) in any way, and we reserve the right to use and disclose such information to our partners, advertisers and any other third parties at our discretion.
If you do not agree or do not consent to the disclosure of your information in any manner described above, you should not use the Services.
We disclose the following categories of personal information for the operational business purposes discussed above:
Identifiers;
Demographics;
Online activity information;
Location information;
Inferences regarding preferences or other characteristics;
Transaction information;
Payment information; and
Audio, electronic, visual, olfactory, or similar information;
We disclose certain personal information in exchange for services, insights or other valuable consideration.  California law treats such sharing as a “sale” even if no money is exchanged.  These disclosures involve:
Identifiers;
Online activity information;
Location information; and
Inferences regarding preferences or other characteristics
Sharing and Disclosure of Information:
Categories of Personal Information
Categories of third parties to whom we may disclose personal information for our business or other permitted purposes
Categories of third parties to whom this information may be sold
Identifiers
Group Companies
Service Providers
Government Authorities
Advertising and Analytics Partners
Demographics
Service Providers
None
None
Audio, electronic, visual, olfactory, or similar information
Group Companies
Service Providers
None
Back To Top
6. WHAT ARE MY CHOICES?
You may opt out of receiving interest-based advertising from us. To find out more about our advertising and how to opt out, please see our Cookies Policy.  You may also choose to block cookies.  Learn more about cookies, how we use them and how to block them by reviewing our Cookies Policy.
You have a right at any time to stop us from contacting you for marketing purposes. When you receive promotional communications from us, you may indicate a preference to stop receiving further promotional communications from us and you will have the opportunity to “opt-out” by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in the promotional e-mail you receive or by contacting us directly at privacy@amcnetworks.com.  Despite your indicated e-mail marketing preferences, we may still send you relationship and/or transactional e-mails regarding the Services, including, for example, administrative confirmations and notices of updates to our Policy, if we choose to provide such notices to you in this manner.
If you access the Services through a mobile device and you do not want your device to provide us with location-tracking information, do not agree to allow your device to share this information with us or disable the GPS or other location-tracking functions on your device, provided your device allows you to do this. Your device manufacturer should provide instructions on how to disable GPS or other location-tracking functions.  If you initially consent to the collection of location information, you can subsequently stop our collection of location information at any time by changing the preferences on your mobile device or by uninstalling the application from your mobile device by following the standard uninstall process to remove applications from your device.
If you are a resident of California, please review the California Rights section below for additional information.
Back To Top
7. HOW LONG DO YOU KEEP MY INFORMATION?
We will hold your personal information on our systems for as long as necessary to provide the relevant Service to you or for so as long as reasonably required to satisfy the purpose for which you submitted the information.
Back To Top
8. WHAT ABOUT LINKS TO THIRD PARTY WEBSITES?
Links to third party websites may be available through the Services. Clicking on such advertisements and links will direct you to the website or application of a third party. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. Any information you provide via those sites is subject to the privacy policies on those websites and is not covered by this Policy. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of each and every website you visit or application you use. This Policy applies solely to information collected by us through the Services and does not apply to third party websites or applications. The ability to access third party information from the Services and to link to other websites and locations from the Services is for your convenience and does not signify our endorsement of such third parties, their products, their services, their websites and locations or the content they make available on the Services or on their websites and locations.
Back To Top
9. HOW IS MY INFORMATION PROTECTED?
We are committed to protecting the security of your information. We use a variety of industry-standard security technologies and procedures to help protect your information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. These measures vary based on the sensitivity of the information that we collect.
It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and devices. Be sure to close your application after using our Services.
Even though we have taken significant steps to protect your information, no company, including us, can fully eliminate security risks associated with information. We cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent every unauthorized attempt to access, use, or disclose your information.
Back To Top
10. WHAT IF MY INFORMATION IS INCORRECT?
You may have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you that identifies you personally. If you live outside of California and would like a copy of some or all of this information, please contact us at privacy@amcnetworks.com. If you live in California, please refer to the California Rights section below for more information. Where permitted by law, we may charge a reasonable fee for this service. We want to make sure that your information is accurate and up-to-date. You may ask us to correct or to remove information that you think is inaccurate. We also provide you with tools and account settings to access or modify some of the information you provided to us and associated with your account.
Back To Top
11. WHAT IS YOUR POLICY REGARDING CHILDREN?
AMC does not direct its Services to children under the age of thirteen (13) and does not knowingly collect information from such children.  We require all users of the Services to be at least thirteen (13) years old.  If we obtain actual knowledge that a user is under the age of thirteen (13), we will promptly delete all information associated with such account.  By using the Services, you are representing that you are at least thirteen (13) years old.
Back To Top
12.  CALIFORNIA RIGHTS.
California law grants its residents certain rights regarding the collection and use of their personal data. Subject to certain limitations, California residents have the right to:
Know about the processing of (i.e., access) personal information collected in the prior 12 months, including learning about the categories and specific pieces of personal information collected, the purposes for which we collect and share personal information, and the categories of parties that may receive personal information.
Right to request the deletion of personal information we have collected about you. We may retain personal information as permitted by law.
Right to opt out of certain disclosures for valuable consideration. You may exercise this right here: Do Not Sell My Personal Information.
California residents may also request and obtain from us once a year, free of charge, a list of the categories of third parties to whom we have disclosed their “personal information” (as defined under California’s Shine the Light law), if any, for their direct marketing purposes in the prior calendar year, as well as the type of “personal information” disclosed to those parties.
We will not discriminate against you for exercising the above-listed rights. We may, however, provide a different level of service or charge a different rate reasonably relating to the value of your personal information.
How to Exercise Your California Rights. If you are a California resident and would like to request access to or deletion of your personal information, please submit your request to privacy@amcnetworks.com. In order to honor your request, we will ask that you provide an email address and contact information which allows us to confirm your identity and avoid fraudulent requests. We verify your identity by matching information you provide with our records. Please note that in the case of requests for deletion, we may need to retain certain personal information to comply with our legal obligations or for other permitted purposes.
You also have the option to designate an authorized agent to submit a request on your behalf. Your authorized agent can submit your request to privacy@amcnetworks.com. For requests through an authorized agent, we require a valid power of attorney or written and signed permission from you. If your authorized agent relies on your written and signed permission, we may need to verify your identity as described above and may contact you directly to confirm that the request is valid.
Back To Top
13. GOVERNING LAW.
This Policy and all disputes arising hereunder or relating hereto shall be governed by, and will be construed under, the laws of the State of New York, U.S.A., without regard to choice of law principles.  Those who choose to access the Services from locations outside the United States do so on their own initiative, and are responsible for compliance with local laws if and to the extent local laws are applicable. AMC may limit the website’s availability, in whole or in part, concerning any person, geographic area or jurisdiction, at any time in its sole discretion.
Back To Top
14. WHERE IS MY INFORMATION STORED AND PROCESSED?
Our services are intended only for individuals located in the United States and Canada. If you visit our Services or contact us from outside of the United States, please be advised that (1) any information you provide to us or that we automatically collect will be stored or otherwise processed in the United States and may be transferred to other jurisdictions; (2) that by using our Services or submitting information to us, you agree to such processing and transfer; and (3) U.S. law may not offer the same privacy protections as those in your country.
Back To Top
15. HOW CAN I CONTACT YOU?
If you have questions or concerns about our Policy, please contact us at: privacy@amcnetworks.com
Back To Top
Are you sure you want to sign out?
Full Episodes Sign In
Choose your provider to watch Live TV & Full Episodes
Need help?
To watch full episodes, you must have a cable provider that supports
BBC America's full episode service and you must have
BBC America
as part of your cable package.
